This README file explains instructions for using the website and changing Bootstrap elements.

Instructions:

The website will only run correctly if you execute main.py LAST and if you're connected to the internet.

How to change styling elements:

1. Base.html contains all styling elements in Bootstrap, the CDN of choice for these web pages.
2. To change the navbar, go to https://getbootstrap.com/docs/4.3/components/navbar/ 
3. If the above link does not work, go to https://getbootstrap.com/docs/ , search for Components and click on Navbar
4. To change the Bootstrap version, go to https://getbootstrap.com/docs  and click on Introduction. Then copy and paste the HTML+JS.
5. For all other styling elements, follow proper HTML styling guidelines.
